Mary Ann Lewis papers
Litchfield Historical Society
- Miscellaneous, 1811-1895
  - Letters received 1853 (Folder 9)
    Handwritten list of letters received [no name to whom they were sent] with initials of senders and dates received in 1853.
  - Letters sent 1853 (Folder 10)
    Handwritten list of letters sent [no name of sender] with initials of to whom they were sent and dates in 1853.
  - Litchfield, Dr. (Folder 11)
    Newspaper article titled "Wedding tactics" from "Gazette" in 1838.
  - "Miscellaneous enigma" (Folder 12)
    Newspaper clipping circa 1855.
  - Phelps, Mary (Folder 13)
    Calling cards for Mary D. Parsons; and Mr. & Mrs. James Hankey.
  - Root, Timothy N, 1811 Mar 28 (Folder 14)
    Notice from Timothy N. Root, Constable to the inhabitants of Farmington (Conn.) to attend Freemans Meeting on April 8th.
  - Smith, Joseph, Jr., 1836 May 13 (Folder 15)
    Small sketch "A view of Manlius Academy, drawn by Joseph Smith Jr. May 13, 1836"
    Also includes a letter from the Onondaga Historical Assoceity of Syracuse, New York to Lockett Ford Ballard, Director of the Litchfield (Conn.) Historical Society, dated 5 Aug 1980 with information about Joseph Smith, Jr. and the Manlius Academy and requesting a film negative of the sketch.
  - Smith, Joseph, Jr. (Folder 16)
    Photograph of the back of the Sketch of Manlius Academy, enlarged postmark from Manlius, NY.
  - Thompson's Lessons [extracts] (Folder 17)
    Handwritten copy entitled "Extracts from Thompson's Lessons page 169th"
  - "To be Forgotten" (Folder 18)
    Handwritten copy of a poem or essay.
  - "The Twelve Months of the Year" (Folder 19)
    A small booklet "The twelve months of the year; with a picture for each month. adapted to northern latitudes." Published by the American Tract Society. Inscribed M.L.P. from D.G.H.
  - [Unknown] (Folder 20)
    Empty envelope from Farmington, Conn. addressed to Miss Mary Ann Lewis, Litchfield, Conn.
  - "Uses of History" (Folder 21)
    Handwritten essay "Uses of History - No.8"
  - "View of the literature of the United States" (Folder 22)
  - Withers, G (Folder 23)
    Newspaper clipping of a poem "Song" by G. Withers. circa 1832.